Can I talk to you?
I saw you when you were dancing.
That's good.
Are you sure when you leave here, you will not go back to your past life?
Because I see you as a harlot.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
In the church, harlot must be delivered.
If I collect thanksgiving or offering from you without delivering you,
I will be punished for that.
Come out, in the name of Jesus!
That spirit of immorality - out!
In the name of Jesus Christ.
If I discover her, and I could not deliver her, then the message is not from God.
If I see you are a thief, anybody can see that.
But to now release that belief by faith, I must show you that God sent me to you by faith.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
You see, that spirit is coming out.
When it is all over, she will be free.
See her.
It is a serious thing. Just leave her, let her get free.
She has been in that job for profit, for many years.
Let her get free.
Hallelujah.
TESTIMONY CONTINUES.
Mrs Paula Santana
Cuban Living In Spain.
My mother is of Nigerian descent and my father is Spanish.
She said her name is Paula and she comes from Spain but originally, she is from Cuba.
Her mother is actually from Nigeria originally - from generations before -
and her father is originally from Spain.
Can you tell us what happened last Sunday?
What was the prophecy you received from Prophet T.B. Joshua?
Mrs Paula Santana
Cuban Living In Spain
Last week Prophet T.B. Joshua gave her a prophecy,
saying that there was a spirit of prostitution in her which she confirmed to be true.
This was something that had been tormenting her life for the past 20 years.
Now she is free.
Can you explain how this spirit entered your life?
When I was about 4 years old, I remember that a relative of my mother used to come to the house
to perform rituals of witchcraft with animals and one day, I was also taken to his house as well.
From there, I began to have nightmares of animals chasing me and men grabbing my neck.
There was always a presence that disturbed me.
When she was very young and growing up in Cuba; when she was about 4 years old,
a relative of her mother came to the house; he was a witch doctor.
He began to do rituals with cowries, charms and animals.
After that she began to dream where she saw animals pursuing her in the dream.
She saw men pursuing her and demons attacking her in her dreams.
When I was 16 years old, I was raped by a policeman who pointed a gun at my neck.
He threatened me saying that if I told anyone, he would kill my parents.
Ever since I was four years old, people used to call me, 'Crazy'. It became my second name.
When she was 16 years old, she was raped by a policeman.
He threatened her that if she told anyone, he would kill her.
So she kept that secret and never told anyone.
From that young age, as well as seeing demons in her dreams,
she would also hear a voice telling her that she was going to run mad.
And very soon, people began to give her that name. Her second name was 'Crazy'.
People would call her a mad woman.
When I was 19 years old, my father was sick with cancer and we were five children.
At this time in Cuba, it was very difficult because there was nothing.
A friend suggested that I should join a modelling agency so I could help my family so I did.
When she was nineteen years old, it was a crisis time in Cuba.
There was nothing to eat; it was a real time of crisis.
There was so much need.
A friend came to her and said, "Paula, why don't you start modeling?
This can help your family because you have a good stature. You can go into modelling".
So she started to do that.
When I arrived at the place, I realised that it was not really what they had told me
but that it was more like a brothel with a different outlook but still the same.
So, I started doing prostitution and in that place, I met my first husband when I was 19 years old.
I got pregnant for him and gave birth to a baby girl
but when she was one week old, he disappeared from my life.
I went back to prostitution and shortly before this, I had been initiated into santeria (witchraft).
I took the decision to follow that route so I did it.
What she thought was just modelling, when she arrived at the place,
it was like a club; it was actually a prostitute house.
So she found herself doing prostitution.
This continued and she actually got initiated into witchcraft.
One day she went to a place and they initiated her with 'santeria'.
which is a witchcraft religion in Cuba.
One day she met a man who came to the place where they were doing prostitution.
He was a foreigner and a lot older than her.
He impregnated her and when the baby was born, he abandoned her.
I entered into santeria (witchcraft) because I was told that I would leave Cuba and
I would not go mad like I had been told since I was small, so I was initiated.
Truly, I left Cuba and went to Spain when I was 23 years old.
When I met my husband, he was 47 years old and I was 19 years old.
When she entered into the witchcraft and they did the ritual,
it was for her to leave Cuba; that was why they were doing the ritual.
And also for her not to go crazy because she always heard a voice telling her
that she was going to run mad.
So in order for her not to go mad and for her to be able to leave Cuba,
that was why they did that ritual.
Soon after that, that was when the man came and took her away to Spain
and that was how she left Cuba.
Soon after arriving in Spain with my first husband, I lost affection for him
and had relationships with young men like me.
There was something that pushed me to go out to the streets and go to clubs.
This spirit of prostitution continued tormenting me as men kept following me
and I continued seeing animals biting me in my dreams. This went on for years.
When she went to Spain, this spirit of prostitution continued to torment her.
Although in the physical, she was married to her husband,
but she continued to have relationships with different men
because this spirit of prostitution continued to torment her.
She would see animals in her dreams, she would see men coming to sleep with her in her dreams,
and people would look at her as if she was a prostitute.
It was then that I met my second husband and I began attending church again.
I had abandoned the church for long because of my involvement in witchcraft.
However, this demon always tormented me - e.g. I would leave the house, dressed normally
but men would pursue me and the cars would stop because of me and I didn't know why.
I would ask myself why men continued to stare at me and hoot their cars.
I didn't understand but men would stop their cars and make indecent proposals to me
and I would even be dressed more decently than others.
Now I understand that it was that same spirit that was attracting the men.
Also, dogs kept chasing me and I kept having nightmares.
Whilst she was in Spain, the spirit of prostitution kept tormenting her,
to the extent that men would stop their cars in the streets, just to ask to be with her.
It was not normal because she would dress like a normal person, not as a prostitute.
When she walked down the street, men would stop their cars and wanted to sleep with her.
This caused so many problems between her and her husband
because men would always be approaching her.
Not only that, in her dreams, she would be always bitten by dogs.
She would see a dog coming to her, animals coming to her
and men sleeping with her and this continued.
There were days where I woke up and said that I didn't want to be married anymore.
I had everything - a perfect marrriage where my husband loved me and I loved him.
He would ask me, "If we have everything, why do you behave like a mad woman?"
I would suddenly want to leave him, run away from the house or become aggressive.
I would start to say things that didn't make sense.
I would insult him and reject him and didn't want him to come near me.
One day, I even lost affection for him although I loved my husband,
I felt the presence of something that was always in-between us.
Many times, the spirit would fight me or enter him and he would fight me; it was a terrible thing.
Although we had everthing, it was like living in hell.
It was like living in hell because when she married her second husband
and she loved her husband, there was always a satanic presence between her and her husband.
She always felt the presence of someone who would not allow her to love her husband.
Anytime she wanted to be with her husband and show affection towards him,
this spirit would not allow her.
She would become aggressive towards him; she would reject him.
She would fight him, and that spirit always caused division between them.
She would just wake up and say that she didn't want to be married anymore.
That spirit would want her to run out of the house
and kept telling her that she was going mad, until one day, she even lost her mind.
One day, I was doing exercise with my friend from the Dominican Republic
when she said, "Paula, why don't you come to my house and watch a T.B. Joshua video?"
When she put the video on, I said to her, "Do you really believe this? Remove it!"
She persuaded me to watch it and when I finally did, I was amazed at the presence of God.
I began to cry and within me, I felt a divine connection with The SCOAN and the prophet.
It was something supernatural that happened in my life.
Later the pastors of my church organised the visit to The SCOAN and I was the last one to join.
It wasn't in my plan but it was in God's plan that I would be here in this place.
One day, her friend from the Dominican Republic came to her house and said,
"Paula, why don't you watch T.B. Joshua?"
So she showed her a video of Prophet T.B. Joshua on the internet.
When she watched, she said, "What is this? I don't want to watch this!" and she stopped watching
Later something told her that she should watch again.
And when began watching Emmanuel TV, there was an immediate spiritual connection.
She realised that truly, God is inside this man and this is somewhere where I can be free.
Later she realised that her church was organising a trip to come to The SCOAN.
She was the last person to be appointed to go on this trip.
It was in the plans of God for her to be here.
When I came to the service, I was seated infront and I was praying that the prophet would see me.
I knew that I needed to be free from this strange presence that was always with me.
I was seated at the front then I was moved to the back and I was very angry
because I wanted to be infront so I could be seen by the pastor.
Then the Holy Spirit said to me, "Paola, don't be afraid. God will find you wherever you are".
When she came to the service, she sat in the front row
because she wanted to be seen by the man of God.
She just wanted to be free from this spirit of prostitution and this spirit of madness
- these spirits tormenting her.
But suddenly she was moved to the back.
She was so angry and annoyed, thinking, "How can the prophet see me if I'm at the back?"
But the Holy Spirit told her, "Wherever you are, God will locate you today".
Mrs Paula Santana
Prophecy Testimony
It happened for the glory of God. It was my day of freedom, when the chains were loosed.
He came up to me and prophesied, and something happened to my body.
Something strong left me. The only thing I know is that I fell to the floor.
I have not seen the video but I just remember that there was a voice tellilng me,
"No, my child, sleep; I will not let you go. You are mine" - it was a woman's voice.
When the prophet came towards her and prophesied to her,
all that she can remember is that she fell under the influence of the Holy Spirit.
She can't remember anything, except that she heard a voice telling her,
"No, you are mine; you are my child. I will not let you go".
She felt as if someone was holding her at the arms
and telling her, "No, I will not let you go".
I was free in that moment from all those spirits.
It was a difficult moment but I give thanks to God for choosing me.
That was my moment and I am free from all those demons of my mind.
I am free from hair extensions which I was addicted to before.
I am now a normal woman, I love the way God created me but above all, I love God
who had mercy on me and that is why today, I can give this testimony.
Really, it was her moment, it was her time for deliverance.
She felt such an amazing presence of
God.
Those chains that held her bound for so many years were cut.
Not only that, but she also had this love and too much connection with artificial hair extensions.
After her deliverance, she removed her extensions.
Now that she is free, this is her natural hair, her natural self.
This is the person God has created
her to be; she knows who she is now.
Mrs Paula Santana
Prophecy Testimony
So we give thanks to God for your life and we want to ask you:
Since last week, what are the changes you have noticed after your deliverance?
Mrs Paula Santana
Prophecy Testimony
My mind is totally free. I don't have any more nightmares. No one pursues me anymore.
I don't feel that evil presence anymore.
I can't wait to get home and see my husband and restore what this demon had stolen from us.
I am experiencing the greatest freedom ever in my life.
All these spirits of prostitution and lust have disappeared from my life for the glory of God.
After her deliverance, she is a totally changed person.
Now, she doesn't have those nightmares;
she doesn't feel that demon following her everywhere.
She doesn't feel that spirit of prostitution - it is totally gone.
She cant wait to go back home to see her husband
because now she feels so much affection for him
and she knows that what the demon has robbed in that relationship, God has restored.
She wants to go back and be with him, in Jesus' name.
Mrs Paula Santana
Prophecy Testimony
We thank God for your life and we want to ask you:
What advice do you have for all those watching you all over the world
who are in a similar position that you were in and are not able to break free?
How would you advice them?
Mrs Paula Santana
Prophecy Testimony
From my experience, I would like to advise people to trust in God.
They should watch Emmanuel TV because it was the door that God opened for my deliverance.
God is in this place and there is a man here whose heart is according to the will of God.
A man with a pure and transparent heart that when I looked into his eyes, I saw Jesus.
There is such a strong presence of God here. I encourage people to come here.
This is a piece of Heaven on earth.
This is the best thing that you can experience if you truly open your heart for deliverance.
She wants to advise everyone that from her experience in life,
she wants to tell people that you should trust in God.
Also, you should get connected with Emmanuel TV
because that was the door that God opened for her to receive her deliverance.
Truly, there is power of God in this place.
Prophet T.B. Joshua has a heart that is really in line with God's Word and God's will.
He has such a pure heart and because of that, Heaven has come to earth in this place - The SCOAN.
She recommends everyone to come and receive their deliverance, in Jesus' name.
Mrs Paula Santana
Prophecy Testimony
We thank God for your life and we want to encourage you,
now that you have been delivered by Christ's Word, you should continue to be ruled by that Word
and make that Word the standard for your life, in Jesus' name.
Mrs Paula Santana
Prophecy Testimony
Thank You, Jesus! This anointing is going back with me to the Canary Islands! Amen!
Amen, thank You Jesus. I am taking this anointing with me to my country, in Jesus' name!
TT: Lizz ndung'u 11/09/2018
RV: Mel Flowers 01/11/2018